<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mehdi Senoussi</title>
    <link>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mehdi Senoussi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  I am a postdoctoral researcher in cognitive science @ Ghent University interested in how our mind represents information and flexibly uses it to interact with the world.
Research Interest My research focuses on studying the flexibility of perceptual and mnesic representations at behavioral and neural levels, and the cognitive control mechanisms that allow to flexibly use these information to perform various tasks. I tackle these questions using psychophysical protocols, computational modelling, and neuroimaging (EEG &amp;amp; fMRI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Short bio After a masters degree in Cognitive Science (Cogmaster) in Paris (France), I completed my PhD in Toulouse (France) under the supervision of Leila Reddy and Rufin VanRullen on the flexibility of perceptual representations. I investigated behavioral and neural consequences of short and long-term learning on visual perception, the neural dynamics of visual processing, and the neural representations of visual objects.
Following my PhD I went on investigating how we flexibly use such mental/neural representations for goal-oriented behavior, and cases in which these processes fail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other activities</title>
      <link>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/others/</guid>
      <description>Collective/administrative responsibilities  2019-2021: Responsible for the purchase of two eye-tracking devices for an EEG platform at the Department of Experimental Psychology at Ghent University, and the MRI platform at Ghent University Hospital. Market research, budget calculation, ordering and organization of training provided by the company providing the eye-trackers (SR-Research). Administrative and technical support following the purchase.
 Since 2020: Member of the eye-tracking support group - Department of Experimental Psychology, Ghent University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Articles Preprints of submitted publications  Senoussi, M., Verbeke, P., Desender, K., Loof, E.D., Talsma, D., and Verguts, T. (2020). Theta oscillations shift towards optimal frequency for cognitive control. bioRxiv, 2020.08.30.273706.
 Senoussi, M., VanRullen, R., and Reddy, L. (2020). Anticipatory reinstatement of expected perceptual events during visual sequence learning. bioRxiv, 2020.11.28.402123.
 Pistono, A., Senoussi, M., Guerrier, L., Rafiq, M., Gimeno, M., Péran, P., Jucla, M., and Pariente, J. (2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mehdisenoussi.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Lectures (L), Directed Work (DW), Practical Work (PW).
Total: &amp;gt; 240 Hours in Cognitive psychology, Ergonomics, Tools and Methodology of science, Cognitive Neuroscience, Neurophysiology in French and English
 Ghent University (Belgium) - Total: 100h  Master in Theoretical and Experimental Psychology: Modelling of Cognitive Processes (M1, 27h L and 72h PW; over 3 years from 2018 to 2021) - Presentation of the computational modelling approach in psychology, and implementation of neural network models in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
